<!--
 Copyright 2016 Google Inc.
 
 Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
 you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
 You may obtain a copy of the License at
 
      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
 
 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
 distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
 WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
 See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
 limitations under the License.
-->

<resources>

    <string name="title">Gorillas</string>
    <string name="subtitle">The great apes from Central Africa</string>
  <string name="paragraph1">Gorillas are ground-dwelling, predominantly
    herbivorous apes that inhabit the forests of central Africa.

\n\nThe 360 video below shows gorillas in the Congo rainforest.
  </string>

  <string name="paragraph2">The eponymous genus Gorilla is divided into two
    species: the eastern gorillas and the western gorillas, and either four or
    five subspecies. They are the largest living primates by physical size.

\n\nThe DNA of gorillas is highly similar to that of humans, from 95–99%
    depending on what is counted, and they are the next closest living relatives
    to humans after the chimpanzees and bonobos.

\n\nGorillas\' natural habitats cover tropical or subtropical forests in Africa.
    Although their range covers a small percentage of Africa, gorillas cover a
    wide range of elevations. The mountain gorilla inhabits the Albertine Rift
    montane cloud forests of the Virunga Volcanoes, ranging in altitude
    from 2,200–4,300 metres (7,200–14,100 ft). Lowland gorillas live in dense
    forests and lowland swamps and marshes as low as sea level, with western
    lowland gorillas living in Central West African countries and eastern lowland
    gorillas living in the Democratic Republic of the Congo near its border with Rwanda
  </string>

    <string name="source">Source &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gorilla">Wikipedia&lt;/a></string>

    <string name="app_name">VRViewApp</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="venue">About Gorillas</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome"</string>
    <string name="welcome_title">Welcome to the VR View Codelab</string>
    <string name="welcome_description">Google Codelabs provide a guided, tutorial, hands-on coding experience. Most codelabs will
      step you through the process of building a small application, or adding a new feature to an
      existing application.</string>
    <string name="gorilla_info">Gorillas are ground-dwelling, predominantly herbivorous apes that inhabit
    the forests of central Africa.</string>
    <string name="codelab_img_description">Image of a codelab computer</string>
</resources>
